I'm cold as ice, you're paralyzed
我坠入冰窟，而你却置之不理
It's not your fault
但这并不是你的错
My heart's a blight, a parasite
我的心如枯木，就像寄居于灵魂深处的蛊虫
Is this what you want?
这是你想要的吗？
It's not a feeling, you're part of me, part of me
这不是感觉，你就是我的一部分，属于我的一部分
Some kind of fever, you're art to me, art to me
你让我感到兴奋，你就像我的艺术品，属于我的艺术品
Stop, take a look at me, here
等等，看看我好吗
Are you looking right through me?
你能看透我吗
Stop, I'm a product of fear
停下，我诞生于恐惧
Stop, take a look at me clearly, baby
停下，再仔细看看我，看清我的灵魂吧，亲爱的
If it upsets you, I will set you free
如果这令你感到困惑，我会还你自由
I'M A
虽然我是个
MONSTROSITY
怪物
TAKE A LOOK AT ME
但是我还是只想让你看着我
MONSTROSITY
怪物又如何？
TAKE A LOOK AT ME
看看我
MONSTROSITY
怪物而已
I pay a price, a sacrifice
我以自身为祭，奉上了全部的我
I'm not what you thought
我不是你想的那样
Another side, it's classified
我藏匿着另一隅灵魂，秘而不宣
Would you be distraught?
你会感到心烦意乱吗？
It's not a feeling, you're part of me, part of me
这不是感觉，你就是我的一部分，属于我的一部分
Some kind of fever, you're art to me, art to me
你让我感到兴奋，你就是我的艺术品，属于我的艺术品
Stop, take a look at me, here
等等，好好看着我
Are you looking right through me?
你现在看清了吗？
Stop, I'm a product of fear
停下，我诞生于恐惧
Stop, take a look at me clearly, baby
停下，看着我，看清我的灵魂吧，亲爱的
If it upsets you, I will set you free
如果这让你感到困扰，我会还你自由
I'M A
虽然我是个
MONSTROSITY
怪物
TAKE A LOOK AT ME
但是我还是想让你看着我
MONSTROSITY
怪物又如何？
TAKE A LOOK AT ME
看看我
MONSTROSITY
怪物而已
You can't forget what you are
你无法忘却你的本质
Some kind of madness
你和我是同类
I'm alone in a world that I'm tearing apart
我孤独地活在这个被我亲手撕碎的世界里
Are you looking right through me?
你会来陪我吗？
Play that I won't take it back now
我不会放你走的
If it upsets you, I will set you free
如果这让你感到困惑，我会还你自由
TAKE A LOOK AT ME
看着我
I'M A MONSTROSITY
就算我是头怪物
TAKE A LOOK AT ME
你也要好好的看着我
MONSTROSITY
怪物而已